Hey, you sound cheerful today.
Are you at my place?
I'll finish this, then I'm on my way.
So you are not married.
No.
Lived together?
No, not really.
Never thought of marrying her
in ten years?
Well...
She wanted to pursue her career.
She what?
Are you sure?
But how did she get it?
That's her friend.
I know him.
I didn't know he was associated
with gangsters.
I don't think she knew it.
He may've been in trouble...
...so left it in her care
without telling her what it was.
Drugs?
You mean like cocaine?
Did you find any?
Not really.
I don't know.
No, I don't.
I really don't know.
Why?...
Why commit suicide?
Hello...
Where have you been?
Stop turning off your mobile when you drink
Need to talk about clients
screening tomorrow.
What?
Don't you remember me?
You bit my hand
and left this scar.
You staggered at the platform...
and were almost hit by a train.
So I grabbed you, remember?
Hey.
What was going on then?
What do you want?
Wanna do 'it', or what?
Sex. Don't you know?
Guys, someone wants to have sex with me.
Hi.
Nice to see ya.
Listen up...
I've got an early day tomorrow,
but I've got no time to play
with kids like you.
On top of that, I've got no money, Sonny.
I paid you back.
Paid back.
I think we robbed this guy before.
- Yeah, we sure did.
- We were playing the 'subway game'.
It was Chisato's turn.
He threw us his wallet
and ran away like a dog.
What's it with you today, pop?
Stand up.
Bring your money to our club.
You shouldn't tell him where.
Oh, he means no harm to us.
'Cause he's a chicken shit.
Don't do anything funny,
or you'll be in trouble.
I'm already in deep shit.
Even a worm turns, so to speak
Ain't that right, Chisato?
Kiriko...
how did you get the gun?
How the hell did you get it?
What's so funny?
Our clients looked very satisfied.
My grand daughter's eyes are glued
to the TV whenever...
your commercials are on.
Goda, make yourself available
for next one, will you?
Sure.
- Well, then...
- See you.
He looks better.
Even at the loss of his girlfriend,
he doesn't take even a day off.
- You know...
- Yes?
How does one get a gun here?
What?
Oh that...
"Toy Gun Shop"
Shut your goddamn mouth up.
Sorry!
- Hold it right there.
- Ok.
You got any idea how much a gun costs?
How much?
2 million for a gun and
500,000 yen for 5 bullets.
How much is it all together?
2.5 million yen.
You got that right.
I'll get you the money tomorrow morning.
This is a deposit.
Umm...
You got a 'chief special'?
This is strictly between us.
If you got any problem,
come to me first.
Don't talk with anyone in the syndicate.
How has your son worked out so far?
He's just fine.
He used to be wild and got into fights...
when he was your son's age.
Me?
I don't remember.
You don't say.
But I think no one could've kicked
your ass when you were that age.
I was much younger.
The time was right after World War II.
No training needed then,
it was the way of life.
So much for my past.
You came to see my son?
Come on in.
Shigeo, your friends are here.
Hi. Please take this.
When you gonna rob somebody,
make sure he's weaker.
Thanks for your help then.
'Chief Special'
No, no. I don't have it,
but I've got 'speed' and 'weed'
What's 'speed'?
It's 'shabu'.
You mean methedrine?
Good evening.
Thought you were at work. What's this?
Ringo Kid: Dismantle a gun.
Use tin foil to pass the custom check.
Jun Wayne: Import some parts,
then you can reassemble a gun.
Better Tomorrow: Someone made
a real gun out of an old toy.
You mean illegally made?
Can't give you a receipt.
It's a toy gun, right?
Don't make any trouble for me.
The same size as this?
Yes, the size of a pencil holder.
This, too, the same size,
using this material...
I see.
I want to use it for a long time.
So please make it strong.
Wow, Idei gave us a lot.
Don't be an 'amateur'.
Here is your ticket to heaven.
You should try this, Goto.
I got it, Sugar.
You're stuck with real hard job, Honey.
It ain't a Utopia here.
Forget about ideal.
Then you start to feel better.
You got the money, pop. Good!
Where the hell are they?
Tell me!
I'll break their necks!
What's going on there?
That hurts, man!
Don't make the scene at my club.
Who's this guy?
He's nobody.
Get outta here, jerk!
- Did that jerk scare you?
- Not a chance.
Good girl, good.
How did you get this scar?
I got it recently.
The best I've ever felt.
I threw myself...
into a moving car.
What about this?
That's nothing.
A punk stabbed me with a knife.
Why do you take speed alone?
I don't want anyone to see me...
just like I'm eating or having sex.
You'll die...
'Chisato Will Die at Midnight Tomorrow'
Who the hell cares!
What do you want from me?
What's it about tomorrow?
None of your business.
Tell me what'll happen?
It's a group of punks.
They're pushing us around...
so we'll whack 'em.
Where is it?
You want a day off?
You want me to tell it to our boss?
Are you out of your mind?
Goda... hello...
Hey!
You!
What's going on there?
What's that shitty face for?
Who the hell you think that car belongs to?
Get rid of him fast.
Shit! He's fucking heavy.
Me?
I'll find work like anybody else.
Can't go on like this forever.
I'll go to college
to study science and engineering.
- You know what?
- What?
I'll bring a bat with lots of
nails stuck in as a weapon.
How about yours?
Mine?
My fists will do.
I'll blow 'em away with my punches.
- Hope we can work together.
- I do, too.
I am off this way.
See you.
Listen, Goto.
Teach those punks a real lesson tonight.
Show 'em how serious we are.
You ain't scared, are you?!
Idei...
...I'll kill 'em for sure.
I was told you've got guns!
Give me a break!
No guns here.
Please! Sell one to me!
I want a 'Chief Special'.
I need it!
I've been watching you.
You'll get this if you do me a favour.
Marry me.
I can't go back to my country now.
I need more money to live here.
More and more.
I need a visa to stay here,
so getting married is the answer.
Let me ask you a question.
Was it his gun,
the guy who was killed?
He said to forget him if he died.
That's what I am doing now.
Do I sign and put my stamp here
I can be your 'wife' sometimes.
This is our wedding ceremony.
Kiriko...
There're a lot more punks than us.
We'll manage.
It's a matter of when we hit 'em.
Listen, Goda. You take care of that
tough lookin' guy.
Forget about the rest.
Well, let's see... you and you...
Move your asses now.
You get back in the car.
Hey, get back and stay there.
Meet me at our base!
Meet me there, guys!
I'm coming you, Sucker!
Get ready for my fists.
Here they come!
Take that shortcut!
These guys got no guts.
'CHISATO WILL DIE'
Hold it right there!
Let's see...
So it looks like we got into a gun fight.
In that case...
Carry this guy to my club.
Take this one back to his place.
Chisato and Goto, you do that.
Don't take him to hospital.
Make sure you grab that thing...
on your way out.
Hey...
You wanna die?
Did you send this to Goto?
I've been watching you.
Who did you send it to?
Take it easy on that speed, will you?
I never touch.
What?
That shit.
I've never done it.
What's on your mind?
Don't go too far.
What do you care?
Why are you...
always in the fast lane?
Mind your own business.
My girlfriend...
died here.
Why did she...
kill herself?
All right, sucker! I tell you why.
It was you who killed her.
It's your fault.
You don't know you're such
a selfish bastard!
You care only about yourself and...
will never understand her feelings.
But then again, it's not only you.
I know there're many people
like you in this world.
They all killed her.
Go ahead.
Pull the trigger!
Do it yourself.
No, I didn't mean it.
Like you said...
I am the one who
didn't want to get married
Never mind. It's not your fault.
I've never taken marriage seriously.
I think I've been trying not
to see things that are important to me.
People have kids because they need
a reason to keep living.
Or else I'll get lost just like a kite
in the wind without a string.
This is an answering machine...
...so please leave your
message after the tone.
Goda, it's about the assignments.
I found a director to do the commercials.
Kiriko...
my string...
will break soon.
Let's have...
our own kid.
Give us your money now!
Who do you think you are?
Grab it.
Hey, the whole town knows
what you're doing.
Keep it down...
...will you?
Go out and shoot the bum
under the highway.
That bum stinks.
Do it quietly.
Goto, you go.
Congratulations on your job.
Who you're staring at?
We all know about it.
A business suit will look good on you.
Never mind the bum.
Kill anyone who disgusts you...
and then you can redeem
your honour.
In your dreams,
you kill people but don't get caught.
The whole thing about Tokyo is a dream.
We are all in the fucking dream.
...please leave your
message after the tone.
Hello...
Goto has been standing...
at a place with a gun in his hand
for an hour.
If he gets caught with the gun...
you will never get it again.
You care less now?
No...
...I do care.
I need it for once.
Where is he now?
In front of a police station.
Are you sure about that?
Of course I am.
I'm here now.
He's right there.
Goto was riding his bicycle...
...but that cop thought he stole it
and treated him like a criminal.
The cop is just a dirty-mind
in a uniform.
Goto hates a man in uniform
who looks down on others.
Hey, you!
Hold it right there.
Yes?
There you are again.
That bicycle looks different
to the one you had before.
Where to?
Come over here.
Come here, I said.
You come here.
You say what?
Let see...
You covered the registration number
with paint here.
See? I can't let you go free.
You'd better come with me.
Let's talk somewhere else.
Shut the fuck up. My time is too
precious for a punk like you.
Excuse me...
That punk!
Hello.
Stop this shit.
Give it to me.
That's mine.
No way.
Maybe you'll do.
Shit!
I'm in chaos.
It would be easier to give the gun back.
It takes years of training to turn
one's body into iron like yours.
Where the hell are you?
Hey, tell me!
Hey!
Gang's fight?
A boxer was shot to death.
A boxer!
Our business has made us a lot of enemies.
But in this case...
shooting the boxer
just might be the end of all of us.
Radar captures our movements
by 0. I seconds and...
calculates the subsequent moves
up to two years in a row.
That means we can't fight our destiny.
The door...
was open.
I want to...
ask you a favour.
Two of our guys were killed.
The rest can't step out of the club.
It's only a matter of time
'till the shooter finds us.
- Is it too much to ask of you to join
me against the shooter? - I'll do it.
I'm scared.
We won't do it then.
It's not that.
I am scared 'cause what if I make it?
What's next?
You don't know what you're doing!
Why him?!
Do you really think he'd be any help?
You gave him the gun!
He may be the one who killed our friends!
Do you hear me?!
Don't worry,
I won't use it on you.
Let him help us.
If that's what he wants to do.
You'd better do what you like.
We're stuck in an endless game.
What's wrong with you?!
Hey, Chisato.
You'd better take a rest.
Hey.
No, mum!
I won't be home for dinner.
Kids...
don't play bad games.
Well...
let's get outta here.
So long.
Shinya Tsukamoto as Goda
Kirina Mano as Chisato
Tatsuya Nakamura as ldei
Takahiro Murase as Goto
Kyouka Suzuki as Kiriko
Hisashi lgawa as Shooter
Executive Producer, Cinematographer, Lighting;
Production Designer and Editor: Shinya Tsukamoto
Music: Chu Ishikawa
Assistant directors: Kiyohide
Otani, and Shinichi Kawahara
Assistant Camera: Michiya Tenma
Costume: Hiroko lwasaki
Gun Creator: Kan Takahama
Special Make Up: Takashi Oda
Producer for Foreign Affairs: Kiyo JOO
Translation: Kiyo JOO
Written and Directed by Shinya TSUKAMOTO
All rights reserved by Kaijyu
Theater Co., Ltd. 1998